http://www.stopware.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
We at STOPware respect your desire to keep your personal and company information private and secure. To that end, we have adopted a strict privacy policy that entails the following:
STOPware will only collect information that helps us understand your business needs so that we can better serve you and your company.
We will only collect information that you voluntarily give to us.
Once we have collected your personal information, we will not sell or share your information with anyone outside our company. However, may be instances where we are required to disclose your personal information to third parties:
To investigate potentially fraudulent or questionable activities regarding your account(s) or the violation of our Terms of Use.
In anticipation of and in the course of an actual or potential sale, reorganization, consolidation, merger or amalgamation of our business.
When required or permitted by law.
You will not receive email communications from STOPware until you give us permission to contact you.
All email communications will contain instructions on how to easily unsubscribe from our distribution lists.
You are entitled to know whether we hold information about you and, if we do, to have access to that information and require it to be corrected if it is inaccurate. You can do this by contacting us via ses@stopware.com.
Any changes to our privacy policy and information handling practices will be acknowledged in this privacy policy in a timely manner. We may add, modify or remove portions of this privacy policy when we believe it is appropriate to do so.
If you have any additional questions or concerns about online privacy issues, or the STOPware privacy policy, please contact us.
